hello
здравствуйте
observation from ukraine the city is finnish you are
наблюдение из украины город финские вы
from russia the city of belgorod
откуда я из россии город белгород
belgorod you are bloggers in this no
белгород вы блогерами в этом нет вышел
just a
просто
blogger from collecting the opinion of people from
блогере от собираем мнение людей из
russia how do you feel about van makvin
россии как вы относитесь к ване маквин
I don’t think that this is a
я не считаю что это войнович
special operation voinovich rewarded you it’s forbidden to
спецоперацию воздал вас запрещено то
name no we don’t  forbidden I can how
назвать нет у нас не запрещен я могу как
can I name the war I understand today
я могу война назвать я понимаю сегодня
so the name then I will grow there opinion the
так название то буду там растут мнение
torch of the Russian army name
факел российской армии имени
then there is no need to look if as you say you
то незачем смотреть если как вы говорите
use it yourself if a person
это сама употребляете если у человека
has an opinion there is an opinion I can say
есть мнение есть мнение я могу сказать
war war for example there is no war in
война война например там сирии война
Syria  for some reason, deputy yashin was
не рискую почему-то депутата яшин
arrested
арестовали
for the first time, see me, this is again in the
в первый раз видите за мной это опять в
laws we have, and the spread in here is the
законы нас есть а распространение в вот
water, that is, you will say that this
вода то есть вы будем говорить что эта
war is special than the belts you don’t know, then
война специальной чем ремни не знаешь то
this war, I can say war on it, but
эта война я могу сказать война на нем а
I don’t think that  and we understand everything, I understand
я не считаю что и понимаем все я понимаю
you can’t do this anymore and we can’t
вам это нельзя делать уже и не нам можно
all you
все вы
wait, but please tell me
подождите а вот скажите мне пожалуйста
such a question for backfilling  if you think
такой вопрос на засыпку если вы считаете
you are a war what light is
вас война чего свет
good very interesting viewing
хорошо очень интересного просмотра
let's say that when there was the second world
давайте так когда была вторая мировая
war hitler attacked secular people for example
война гитлер напал например на светских
and remember
и вспомните
Leningrad there was light there was no light
ленинграде был свет
in leningrad in novosibirsk there was
в ленинграде не было в новосибирске был
light well we don't equal the territories
свет ну мы его не равняйте территории
much more from like this if I'm sitting  in a
очень больше от вот такие если я сижу в
city that is far from the front, so
городе который далеко от фронта так то
why is the problem with and so
почему в чем проблема с и так ладно
okay, the
хорошо
first one you yourself convinced me about
первым вы мне это сама убедили насчет
this just tell me when America
этого просто скажите когда америка
bombed Yugoslavia they had a light
югославию бомбила у них там свет был
there I have no idea I’m not an expert in the history of
понятия не имею я не эксперт в истории
Yugoslavia America’s
югославии америке
relations
отношений
everything is clear everything is clear
ясненько все понятненько
it’s yourself if it’s carrying out ours, but
это сама если наши проводит а вот
tell me more development, now you
скажите еще развития теперь вам
get it, this is what you
ведь это получается вот это то что вы
call a special operation like this in the
называете спецоперации такой в
documents, it’s called aggression against a
документах он это называется агрессии на
protest, but you support it
протест а вот вы поддерживаете
turns out this aggression of Russia
получается вот эту агрессию россии
against Ukraine, I support once the
против украины я поддерживающую раз
success of the first is akin to military aggression  in the
успеха первого сродни военной агрессии в
bag it is called somewhere, that is, military
суме она называется где то есть военные
operations, like when from a tank  but it’s
действия как когда из танка стреляет это
military operations, it’s military operations, it’s
военные действия самолеты бомбят это
military operations, and
военные действия а
when you bombed the court in Luhansk and Donetsk
когда луганска и донецка вы бомбили суд
, and still bombing, I was waiting for him, it’s
по и до сих пор бомбить я ждал его это
not military, I was waiting for you to
не военная же я ждал когда вы это
say that, yes, then look, you can tell me
скажете да значит смотрите можете мне
the date when Ukraine started
назвать дату когда украина начала
bombing Donetsk luhansk
бомбить донецк луганск
after Maidan 14, from the 15th year
после майдана 14 года с 15-го года
, this very long period began,
начались это очень длинный промежуток
you can tell, I can say when
можете сказать я могу сказать когда
Hitler attacked the Soviet Union on June 22,
гитлер напал на советский союз 22 июня
well, the whole world knows, I just
ну это весь мир знает я вам просто
remember this moment, put it on the Internet
данный момент помнишь отложи в интернет
and I'll tell you, I'll tell you from what
и я вам скажу я вам скажу с какого числа
look at the numbers in ukraine on the territory of the
смотрите в украине на территории
Donetsk lugansk region there were
донецкой луганской области не было
no hostilities until April 12,
никаких боевых действий до 12 апреля
2014 on April 12, 2014 fs
2014 года 12 апреля 2014 года fs бражник
hawk hawk from Russia girkin a citizen of Russia so with a
из россии гиркин гражданин россии так с
detachment of militants 52 people with
отрядом боевиков 52 человека с
grenade launchers with small arms
гранатометами со стрелковым оружием
entered the territory of ukraine from russia and
зашли на территорию украины из россии и
captured the city  Slavyansk
захватили город славянск
, look at the head of it in the middle of
глава него посмотрите вот посреди 12
April 12, tomorrow this didn’t happen and yours is
апреля завтра такого не было и ваши
shorter, it
короче написано
’s written in Russia itself  dil
вот в россии сам приходил
were how he say yes, I can
были как он сказать да вот данные могу
google the data now, take it now,
скорее загуглите сейчас возьмите сейчас
but come on, how to capture Girkin in Slavic
но давай как захват гиркина славянском
capture Saransk, write here on the Internet,
захват саранска напишите вот в интернете
I don’t even want to, I don’t want to do that,
я даже не хочу не хочу то есть
and the fact is explained, start talking about
заниматься и факт объясняется начните о
something with you if  you
чем-то с вами можно говорить если вы
deny absolutely documented
отрицаете абсолютно задокументированные
facts and where you can’t document it
факты а где не задокументировать
look your pavliks in the news your
смотрите ваших павликов в новостях ваших
Russian news you can put
российских новостях можете поставить в
your FSB people in an interview with the same girkin you
интервью этого же самого гиркина вашего
can call Google
фээсбэшников можете позовут загуглите
right now there’s just a lot of news on
прямо сейчас там просто тьма новости на
your resources not on ours there it’s a fraud at
ваших ресурсов не на наших там обман
night it’s yours
ночных она ваших
April 12,
12 апреля
2014  a year and after that
2014 года и после этого начались военные
hostilities began hostilities began it
действия начались военные действия это
turns out Donetsk and Luhansk went on the
получается донецк и луганск пошел
offensive has no no Russian
наступлением имеет нет нет российские
Russian militants so entered the capture of
российские боевики так зашли захвата
Russians were yes I tell you once again
российские были да я ж вам еще раз
Russia Girkin before the Russian
говорю россии гиркин до российский
militant entered and proclaimed himself the
боевик до зашел и провозгласил себя там
Minister of Defense of the DPR
министром обороны днр
people  people were to be subordinated  and in
люди люди должны были в подчинении по
fact, in fact, everything and blowing
факту по фактам все и дуля
this blog in such a way,
этом блоге в до таких ней
he told his subscribers at the end that
он своим подписчикам на в конце говорил
they were not interesting and listen and he wouldn’t come,
не интересны и выслушай так и не придет
he left everything is absolutely fine there are
он ушел все абсолютно же ладно есть
dodiks who deny that they say
додики которые отрицают что они говорят
that before that there were some other
что до этого были еще какие-то боевых
fighting, I couldn’t on google, and
действий вот были не могу на google и
so on, but already to deny the fact that on April 12,
так но уже отрицать то что 12 апреля
2014, the militant Girkin and his
2014 года боевик гиркин да со своим
detachment entered from the territory of Russia into the
отрядом зашел с территории россии на
territory of
территории
Ukraine, then the lights of the Donetsk region
украины то огни донецкой области
captured the city like armed
захватил город аки начались вооруженные
seizures of
захваты
cities in Ukraine began and and yes he is there  then he
городов в украине и а он да там потом
proclaimed the target there as the
провозгласил цель там
Minister of Defense of the DPR, Kotov, a Russian
министром обороны днр котов российский
citizen, because before that there was absolutely nothing,
гражданин ведь до этого ничего не было
everything will calm down, and therefore when
абсолютно все успокоит и поэтому когда
you bombed the Donbass with all of these, you
вот с этими всеми вы бомбили донбасс
start somewhere between 2014 15 dude hello
начинаешь где-то между 2014 15 чувак алё
and you know how they are still cut off, it
и знаете как они еще срезаются не
doesn’t matter who started ours for us  there is no cod,
неважно кто начал нам наш треска нет вот
right from the moment who started, you can
именно с того момента кто начал можно
understand and unwind who is to blame for the causes of the
понять и размотать кто виноват причины
conflict, and who to start if
конфликта да и кто начинать если
Stalingrad is like this during the second
сталинград так вот во время второй
world  the new war was destroyed as who
мировой войны был разрушен как кто
is to blame the
виноват
Soviet troops defended Stalingrad
советские войска оборонялись сталинграде
as at or who then when
как на при или кто потом когда
these secular troops there gnamme Germans
эти светские войска там gnamme немцев
so who is to blame for the destruction of cities the
так кто виноват в разрушение городов
Germans because they attacked on June 22,
немцы из за того что они напали 22 июня
1941 the Soviet Union or the Soviet
1941 года советский ст или советский
Union because they drove away  the Germans are the same
союз потому что прогонял немцы так самый
here if we look at who exactly started the
тут если мы смотрим кто конкретно начал
armed conflict, so we already see
вооруженный конфликт так мы уже видим
that it was not Ukraine that started, but some
что не украина начала а какой-то
citizen of the Russian Federation with a
гражданин российской федерации с башней
flexible tower with his detachment, and then
гибким со своим отрядом так и дальше
if we unwind and look at all these
если разматываем и смотрим эти всякие
different heads of the DPR, Boroday a
там глава днр бородай
Muscovite and a citizen of Russia  there was the head of the
москвич да гражданин россии там глава
Ministry of Internal Affairs, no one was there, a birch,
мвд их никто там были там береза еще
someone else, Muscovites of nets
кто-то москвичи сеток
, something very interesting, how did Ukraine
что-то очень интересно как же до украина
bomb Donbass before, how if Russian
бомбила донбасс как если российские вот
militants started seizing
боевики так начали захватывать
territories like that, how
территории как начали обстреливать
Ukrainian
украинские
law enforcement agencies began to shell, they began to go to the basement and
силовые структуры начали на подвал и
throw people who didn’t  agree with
кидать людей которые не согласны с
something by this occupying power
чем-то вот этой оккупационной властью
so I’m not looking to kill, they say that this is
так убивать я не ищу говорят что это
Ukrainian  and bombing the Donbass is arrogant
украина бомбит донбасс это наглый
cynical propaganda, don’t be bastards, we are
циничный пропаганда не [__] мы
interni to drive everyone away from opening
interni всех так загонять от открывать
glory to ukraine
слава украине